[THUNDERCLAP]
[BUZZER SOUNDING]
[PHONE DIALING]
[RINGING]
WOMAN: Hello.
Hey, I'm on my way,
and don't forget my money.
See you soon. And, Bailey,
Don’t you forget.
[HORN HONKS]
Shit.
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
Curiosity killed the cat.
[BEEPS]
Shit.
[RADIO STATIC]
[GASPS]
Jesus.
[GARBLED TRANSMISSION]
[TRANSMISSION STOPS]
[SCREAMS]
[HORN HONKING]
Cool.
Well, hello, dolly.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ What are you
thinking about ♪
♪ Who do you
think you are ♪
♪ Oh, rage in the cage
and piss upon the stage ♪
♪ There's only one sure way
to bring the giant down ♪
♪ Defunct the strings
of cemetery things ♪
♪ We're one flat foot
on the devil's wings ♪
♪ Crawl on me
sink into me ♪
♪ Die for me
living dead girl ♪
♪ Crawl on me
sink into me ♪
♪ Die for me
living dead girl ♪
♪ What are you
thinking about ♪
♪ Who do you
think you are ♪
♪ Oh, raping the geek
and hustling the freak ♪
♪ Like a hunchback juice
on a sentimental noose ♪
♪ Operation filth, they love
to love the wealth ♪
♪ Of an S.S. whore
making scary sounds ♪
♪ Crawl on me
sink into me ♪
♪ Die for me
living dead girl ♪
♪ Crawl on me
sink into me ♪
♪ Die for me
living dead girl ♪
♪ Ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo ♪
♪ What are you
thinking about ♪
♪ Aw, crawl on me
sink into me ♪
♪ Die for me
living dead girl ♪
♪ Blood on her skin ♪
♪ Dripping with sin ♪
♪ Do it again ♪
♪ Living dead girl ♪♪
Hello. I'm Chief Kincaid,
Jade's uncle.
David Collins.
Nice to meet you, sir.
David, come on in.
Jade, David's here.
Well, I've been hearing
good things about you, David.
I understand you're off
to Princeton next fall.
Yes, sir.
What are you
going to study?
Theater Arts.
Mmm-hmm. But on an athletic
scholarship, right? Playing hockey?
Figure skating.
Mmm-hmm.
Jade!
Warren, don't scream.
Hi.
You look great.
Jade, I have to tell you.
This guy is a big improvement
over the last one.
I think your mother and
father would have agreed.
My parents liked
all my friends.
[SIGHS]
I'll be home by midnight.
She's in good hands, sir.
Uh. . .
You forget something?
Oh.
This is for you.
I love lilies.
Actually, it's an orchid.
Cymbidium orchid.
You put it in a vase and drop
an aspirin in the water,
it should last you
the whole week.
Or so I read.
Nice meeting you.
[WHIMPERS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[INSECT BUZZING]
[DIALING]
She just left.
[GASPS]
You look beautiful.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
So Warren fell for it?
Mmm-hmm.
David made quite an impression.
I think Warren's in love.
Yuck. Not my type. I'm so over
that whole uniform thing.
I won't go home now, mama
Don't make a fool of me
You see, I am
the boogie-woogie...
[SIREN CHIRPS]
Christ. It's Needlenose.
[ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PARKING BRAKE SETS]
Gotcha. [CHUCKLING]
[CHANTING]
Give me the power,
I beg of you.
[CHANTING]
Give me the power,
I beg of you.
[CONTINUES CHANTING]
Awake.
Awake!
Awake! Awake!
What a crock.
[THUNDERCLAP]
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
Hey, Tiffany.
What are you doing here?
Come on. Let me in. I'll
catch my death out here.
Promises, promises.
[COUGHS]
Whoa. Whoo!
Hey, how was your day?
Same old, same old.
Hey, check it out.
What?
Check it out.
What is it?
You mean, "Who is it?"
Who is it?
You mean, "Who was it?"
[GASPS]
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. You really did a
number on him, didn't you?
[CHUCKLING] What did you use?
Was it really bloody?
Did he scream a lot?
Was he half. . .
You know, Damien, this guy
looks awfully familiar.
I recognize the nail polish.
Shit.
You never really actually
killed anybody, did you?
Did you? Did you?
You pathetic worm !
Come on, Tiff.
I'm working up to it.
Oh, man.
You know, it took me 10
hours to make that thing.
Damien.
Yeah?
Could you do me a favor, and see if
my lipstick is under the sofa there?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Back on your knees.
Crawl.
Good boy.
Stay down on the floor
where you belong.
That's right.
There's nothing under here.
[GASPS]
Charlotte.
How did you get out?
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
[MOANING]
Oh!
Ugh!
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
Tiffany?
[GASPS]
Well, here we are.
How long have we been
going out for now, huh?
What?
Don't you think you've kept
me waiting long enough?
No.
Oh.
You know what the
French call an orgasm?
[SPEAKS FRENCH]
[SCOFFS]
The little death.
Come on, Tiffany.
Let's die a little.
[THUNDERCLAP]
[TIFFANY SCREAMS]
Ah! [SCOFFS]
Hi. I'm Chucky.
Wanna play?
Where the hell did
you get this thing?
Got him from the cops.
He's the actual doll from those murders.
I stitched him together.
You got to be kidding me.
No, I'm not kidding you.
Why would I kid you?
Come on, Tiffany.
I knew you were obsessed.
I'm not. . .
But Chucky? He's so '80s.
No, he's not.
He isn't even scary.
Yes, he is.
Look at him. What are
you looking at, punk?
You looking at me?
[LAUGHING]
All right.
So, I was wrong.
I thought he'd make
an interesting toy.
Damien?
Huh?
You wanna play?
Okay.
First, I do this.
Are you ready for
a ménage à trois?
What's that?
I thought you
understood French.
Ow!
[LAUGHING]
Now you watch me.
Both of you.
You know, Damien, there's something
I never told you about Chucky.
Don't tell me Schmucky is one of
those dolls who wets his pants.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah. I wouldn't talk
that way about Chucky if I were you.
He has a very bad temper.
Ooh!
You see, we lived
together for years.
Of course, that was before
the cops killed him.
That was before he passed his
soul into that doll there.
[LAUGHING]
Boy, was he ever jealous.
Anybody even looked at me,
Chucky would take care of him.
Wouldn't you, Chucky?
We were gonna get married.
God, was he
an incredible lover.
He was the best
I ever had.
Come on, baby.
He ain't big enough to take
care of a woman like you.
[THUNDERCLAP]
It ain't the size that counts, asshole.
It's what you do with it.
[SCREAMS]
All right.
[LAUGHING EVILLY]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
Hi.
How you been?
Okay.
You?
Peachy.
Actually, to tell you the truth,
I've been kind of out of it.
I know. It took me
10 years to find you.
That is sick.
What are you doing
with this jerk anyway?
Ten years is
a long time, Chucky.
Besides, I was never actually with him.
You know me.
I'll kill anybody, but I'll
only sleep with someone I love.
You look great, Tiff.
Thanks.
I mean it.
I gotta be honest.
I always thought you were
gonna let yourself go.
Come here.
Yeah.
Huh?
[CHUCKLING]
[LAUGHING] Stop it.
[BEEPING]
Hmm.
Are you satisfied?
Can I wait in the
car, please? No.
[SIREN CHIRPS]
All right, Boogie Nights,
you're up.
This is such
a load of shit.
You know we haven't
been drinking.
Well, then you've got nothing
to worry about, do you?
[BEEPING]
Evening, Chief.
Seems like
a false alarm here.
That's okay, Norton. Better
safe than sorry, right?
This is a new low.
For you, too.
Get in the car.
Bite me.
Jade, when you're 18, you can
go to hell, for all I care.
But until then,
I'm stuck with you.
And I'll be damned if I'm
gonna let you embarrass me
by ending up on Jerry Springer
with some trailer trash lowlife.
You fuck.
But you won't.
Not Jade anyway.
Not anymore.
In the car.
You can't keep us
from seeing each other.
I'm the Chief of Police, sport.
I can do whatever I want.
So if, for example, I was to run
a blood test on you tonight,
and the results
made you look like
Christian Slater
on New Year's Eve,
you think anybody
would question me?
He's bluffing.
Try me.
I wish we really could
choose our own families.
David, you keep your
orchid dry now, you hear?
Come on, sunshine.
[LAUGHING]
"Try me."
Screw him.
If I were you, I would take Jade,
get the hell out of Dodge,
and never look back.
Look, Chucky. I made Swedish
meatballs, your favorite.
Honey, you shouldn't have.
Well, I wanted everything tonight
to be absolutely perfect.
Tiff, what the
hell is that?
It's a playpen,
silly, for the nursery.
You know, Chucky,
I still have the ring.
What ring? The ring, the
one you left for me.
I found it on the mantel
the night you were killed.
I've never taken it off.
Oh, that? The one I got
from Vivian Van Pelt.
Vivian who?
Vivian Van Pelt.
I dumped her in
the river, remember?
That ring is worth
five or six grand, easy.
You mean, you weren't gonna
ask me to marry you?
What are you, fucking nuts?
[LAUGHING]
You thought. . .
You haven't changed.
You'll never change.
What the hell
was I thinking?
Now, the first thing we gotta
do is get me out of this body
once and for all.
No.
I think I prefer you
like this.
You're kind of cute. You're
just like a little baby.
Is the little baby
ticklish? Is he?
[LAUGHING] Stop!
Is he? Is he? Is he?
Stop! Stop!
Is he? Is he?
Okay. Mommy's tired.
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
Time to go to sleep.
Okay, I get it.
You're still hung up
on the domestic thing.
No problem.
We'll get hitched.
Sorry. I'm not
into short guys.
[LAUGHING]
[COUGHING]
My mother always said love was
supposed to set you free.
But that's not true,
Chucky.
I've been a prisoner of my love
for you for a very long time.
Now it's payback time.
You let me out
of here right now!
Sweet dreams, asshole.
♪ I'm crazy ♪
♪ Crazy for feelin'
so blue ♪
♪ I knew ♪
♪ You'd love me
as long as you wanted ♪
♪ And someday ♪
♪ You'd leave me
for somebody new ♪
♪ Crazy for tryin' ♪
♪ And crazy for cryin' ♪
♪ And I'm crazy
for lovin' you ♪
♪ I'm crazy for tryin' ♪
♪ And crazy for cryin' ♪
Jesse, honey, could you
give me a hand with this?
Yeah, okay,
just a second.
Thanks, sweetface.
I owe you one.
Yeah.
Shit!
Hi.
So, you moving
out already?
No such luck.
Oh, sorry.
You want me to
put that in the car?
Yeah, I'm just, you know, taking
some stuff to the Goodwill.
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHING]
It's heavy.
Oh, yeah.
What do you got in here?
Oh, you know. A little of
this, a little of that.
Stuff that's gone out of style.
Yeah.
You ever look
at something,
and you realize you are just
sick to death looking at it?
That's how I feel
about that shit.
Here. In the trunk.
In the trunk?
You can do it.
Bend your knees.
Wow. You are strong. Nice muscle tone.
You work out a lot?
I've been doing
some push-ups.
Sorry.
No, that's okay.
Can't hurt it.
Might help.
CHUCKY: Tiffany,
where the fuck are you?
You got some company?
No, just babysitting.
Foul-mouthed little fucker.
Let me help you with this.
So, what are you
doing later on?
'Cause I was thinking
maybe you and I could
go get a drink or something?
That is,
if you're up to it.
No, no. I can't.
Why?
I'm seeing someone.
Really?
All the good guys
are taken.
I gotta go.
Okay.
Bye.
Jesse?
Treat her right, Jesse.
Excuse me?
Treat her right. Never
take her for granted.
It's like my mother
always used to say,
"A woman spends all day slaving
over a hot stove for a man,
"the least he can
do is the dishes."
She's kind of a
philosopher, my mother.
Hmm.
Take it easy.
See you around.
MAN ON SPEAKER:
Spell "woman."
B-I-T-C-H.
That is incorrect. The correct
spelling of "woman" is
W-O-M-A-N.
Shows how much you know.
Yoo-hoo!
I'm home.
Oh! Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
If you can't play nice, I may
just have to take your toys away.
I have a surprise
for you.
I've been thinking about what you
said about wanting to get married.
Yeah? I think it would do
you good to settle down.
Babe, this is great.
You won't regret it,
I promise.
I'm gonna treat
you like a princess.
What's that?
Your bride.
With this ring,
I thee wed.
Oh, Chucky.
She's beautiful.
[LAUGHING]
You are so dead.
Congratulations, Chucky.
Now, I'm sure you two kids
would want to be alone.
WOMAN ON TV: While there are still no leads
in the murder of Officer Bob Bailey,
evidence suggests
that his death may be
linked to another
body found earlier today.
Damien Baylock, whose real
name was Howard Fitzwater,
was dragged from the East
River this afternoon.
Detective Preston, is there a
connection between these two murders?
Could be. Possibly.
We're looking into it.
Is this the work
of a serial killer?
Maybe.
I didn't say that.
No, sir, you didn't, but what can
you tell us about these murders?
Nothing.
I can tell you
that this used to be
a nice, quiet,
rural community...
She's alive! Alive!
[GROWLING]
[LAUGHING]
The bride of Frankenstein.
I promise to love, honor and
cherish till death do us part.
You got that right.
[MOANING]
[SCREAMS]
[LAUGHING]
She hate me.
We belong dead.
[YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
[CHUCKY LAUGHING]
[CHANTING]
Give me the power,
I beg of you.
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
Awake!
[THUNDERCLAP]
What a crock.
[SCREAMING]
You son of a bitch!
What have you done to me?
You got your wish.
You're mine now, doll.
And if you know
what's good for you,
you are going to love,
honor and obey.
I wouldn't marry you if you
had the body of G.I. Joe.
Hey, Raggedy Ann, you looked
in the mirror lately?
Now is not the time
to get picky. Hmm.
[GROWLS]
Face it, Tiff. You need me. Otherwise,
you're stuck like this for good.
I don't need you.
I'll look it up myself.
Oh, go ahead.
Chapter six.
Page 217.
The Heart of Damballa.
What's that?
An amulet.
We need it to transfer our
souls into human bodies.
Okay. And where
the hell is it?
I was wearing it
around my neck
the night those
bastards gunned me down.
It was buried with my corpse
in Hackensack, New Jersey.
All right, let's go.
Oh, sure. I'll steer and
you can work the pedals.
We're dolls, you dope!
Oh, my God!
What are we gonna do?
[CRYING]
Ay-yi-yi.
Shut up.
You shut up.
I don't get it. Why don't
you just mail the dolls?
TIFFANY: These dolls
are very special.
What do you mean,
"special"?
I mean, there's $500
in it for you
if you get them
there by tomorrow.
No questions asked.
I'd do it myself,
but I have to take care of a friend
who's mentally incapacitated.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll do it.
But I want $1,000.
Okay, sweetface,
I can give you half now,
and my friend in Jersey
will give you the rest.
Keys are under the mat.
[BLONDIE'S "CALL ME" PLAYING]
♪ Color me
your color, baby ♪
♪ Color me your car ♪
♪ Color me your color,
darlin' ♪
♪ I know who you are ♪
♪ Come up off
your color chart ♪
♪ I know where
you're coming from ♪
- ♪ Call me ♪
♪ On the line ♪
♪ Call me, call me any, anytime ♪
- ♪ Call me ♪
♪ My love, you can call me
any day or night ♪
♪ Call me ♪
Wow!
Barbie, eat your heart out.
Uh. . . Um. . .
Just act natural.
Right.
- ♪ Call me ♪
♪ My love, call me,
call me any, anytime ♪
- ♪ Call me ♪
♪ My love, call me,
call me for some overtime ♪
"Please deliver dolls to Caretaker's
office, Forest Creek Cemetery.
"Hackensack, New Jersey.
Love and kisses, Tiffany."
Cemetery?
♪ Call me for your
lover's lover's alibi ♪
- ♪ Call me ♪
♪ On the line, call me
call me any, anytime ♪♪
David, you remember when you
were seeing Brad Barker?
Oh! Vividly. Whoo!
You loved him,
didn't you?
Yeah, I did.
What happened?
His mother found a
letter I'd written him.
She freaked, and we
haven't spoken since.
You know, Jade,
we get very few chances
in life to be happy.
You gotta grab the brass
ring when you can.
We don't have time
for this shit.
Jade, I need
to talk to you.
Hey, Jesse.
JESSE: Hey, David.
I want details.
Jesse, Warren will be home any second.
If he catches you. . .
Jade, you know I'll never
take you for granted.
Jesse. . . You know, like if you'd
cook, I'd do the dishes, right?
What are you
talking about?
I'd do anything for you,
anything at all.
You know that, right?
Right?
[SCOFFS]
Yes. Yes, I know.
Then marry me.
What?
Marry me.
Tonight.
Warren would kill us.
I don't care about Warren.
That's why we're
gonna disappear.
Where are we gonna go?
Anywhere you want.
Well, what are we
gonna do for money?
I got money.
Where did you get this?
You know my neighbor,
Tiffany?
She's paying me $500 to take a couple
of dolls to a friend of hers in Jersey.
Jade, there's another
$500 when we get there.
Oh, shit, Jesse. What has
that freak gotten you into?
[LAUGHING] JESSE: I don't know.
I don't care.
I can put a deposit on an apartment.
I'll get a job.
I'll help put you
through college.
I think I'm gonna
throw up.
Jade, marry me.
What do you say?
I say, "I do."
Come on.
Let's get you packed.
Okay.
Aw, that's so romantic.
I give them six months,
three if she gains weight.
[PHONE DIALING]
It's me.
His van is parked right in
front of my house as we speak.
[BEEPS]
Who the hell is this bozo?
What's he doing?
Screwing with our ride,
that's what.
Ah, what the hell.
I need the exercise.
Were you born with that knife
super-glued onto your hand, or what?
What are you talking about?
For God's sake, Chucky,
drag yourself into the '90s.
Stabbings went out
with Bundy and Dahmer.
You look like Martha
Stewart with that thing.
Who the fuck is
Martha Stewart?
My idol.
And what does
Martha tell you to do
when guests drop by for dinner and
you haven't had time to shop?
You improvise.
What about. . .
Predictable.
Hmm. . .
Uh. . .
A-ha!
[TIFFANY LAUGHING]
Who's there?
[CONTINUES LAUGHING]
Ugh!
Now!
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
Why does that
look so familiar?
See? Now, that's the work
of a true homicidal genius.
Not bad, for an amateur.
[DOOR OPENS]
Shit. Here they come.
JESSE: Yeah!
[JADE LAUGHING]
What do we do with him?
I don't know.
What would
Martha Stewart do?
Here.
Come on. Help me.
I am helping.
He's heavy.
[GASPS]
Wait.
Huh?
What's the matter?
I could've sworn
that door was locked.
Come on.
We have to go.
[ENGINE STARTING]
Oh, yeah!
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Give it back
My, my
Shit!
I'm empty
And sad
[SIREN CHIRPS]
Now what?
How you kids
doing tonight?
Going somewhere?
Will you both get out
of the van now, please?
Officer Norton,
I have a question.
All this
following us around. . .
Is that covered by
your regular salary?
Or does my uncle
pay you extra?
Extra.
Look, I'm sure
you're not a bad person.
I know that you're
just doing your job.
But couldn't you just
please give us a break?
You know,
I wish I could.
You seem like
really nice kids.
It's nothing personal,
at least on my part.
But. . . The money.
You're disgusting. Shut up!
[LAUGHING]
Shut up, or I swear to God,
I'll fucking vaporize you.
[CROWD EXCLAIMING]
[COUGHING]
[INHALING]
Ahh!
[GASPS]
Come on. Take it easy.
Take it easy. Come here.
Oh, God. We're never gonna
get away with this.
They're never
gonna let us go.
JESSE: It's gonna be okay.
All right?
Now, why don't you go get us
something to eat for the road,
and I'll deal
with Needlenose.
All right?
Okay.
Ugh!
Ah!
Oh, that's bullshit!
You know this isn't mine.
You're in a lot
of trouble, kid.
Now don't you
fucking move.
Shit! Shit!
Figures you'd hitch us
a ride with the fugitive.
Give me your lighter.
What are you doing?
Improvising.
Now, sit back and
learn from the master.
WOMAN ON RADIO:
Chief Kincaid isn't answering.
What do you mean, "He's not
answering?" I just talked to him.
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Rude fucking doll.
Come on, Jade.
[SNIFFS]
WOMAN: Norton?
Are you still there?
Norton!
Bye!
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMING]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
Jesse!
Jesse! Jesse!
Get in ! Get in.
There they are.
Call the police.
Shit. Shit. Go!
Jesse, drive! Go!
Go!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[HORNS HONKING]
Well, at least
you haven't forgotten
how to show
a girl a good time.
Where were you?
ls that all
you have to say?
What do you
want me to say?
I should think
you'd have something
to say about what
happened back there.
I got something to say.
I think you're fucking crazy.
I'm crazy?
You say you'd do anything for
me, and this is what I get?
Wait a minute. You don't think
that I had anything to do
with that explosion back there?
Didn't you?
No.
To be honest, I was thinking
the same thing about you.
How could you
think that?
You announced in front
of a hundred people
that you wanted
to vaporize him.
Oh, it was
a figure of speech.
Well, you were just as quick
to accuse me. [RINGING]
Hello.
What the fuck!
David, I don't know
what to tell you.
I don't know what the hell
is going on around here.
Well, the cops seem to think
it's all pretty cut and dried.
Think of Mickey and
Mallory, Bonnie and Clyde.
You get the picture?
Mickey and Mallory?
Bonnie and Clyde?
They were mass
murderers, David.
Multiple murderers,
actually.
Mass murders happen all at
once, like at the post office.
Multiple murders
are serial killings.
Am I missing something? Norton
was just one murder, right?
They found a cigarette lighter
next to Norton's car.
Belonged to that cop
who got his throat slashed.
And there's
Another thing.
Jade, your uncle's missing.
What?
Look, I know you two
had nothing to do with this.
But maybe you should turn yourselves
in until they figure it out.
David, are you whacked?
Nobody is gonna believe us.
They're setting up
roadblocks at the border.
You two had better
lay low for a while.
Thanks.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Did you see Warren tonight?
Not since this morning.
Did you?
No.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Our little room on Seventh street
is getting cold ♪
♪ I saw a pattern on a blanket
just the other day ♪
♪ It looked just like
the pillow you threw away ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ I just woke up
the other night ♪
♪ And now I know what to do
I guess I'll see you in hell ♪
♪ Yeah ♪♪
What are you doing?
Do you trust me, Jade?
Of course I do.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Sucker.
I think they make
a cute couple.
And if you ask me, it'd be
a shame to break 'em up,
if you know what I mean.
MAN: Dearly beloved,
we are gathered
here tonight
to celebrate the union of two
people in holy matrimony.
And what God
joins together,
let no man tear asunder.
WOMAN ON RADIO: Violence in
movies and television...
What is this shit?
Never mind...
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Jesus, the music scene's gone
to hell since I've been dead.
[HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING]
That's more like it.
TIFFANY: Isn't it beautiful?
I always dreamed of having
a big church wedding
with bridesmaids and a cake
and my picture in the paper.
Not just the usual mug shot, but
something really flattering.
Tiff?
I'm sorry.
For everything.
Um, I guess
I can't complain.
I mean, I always wanted us
to spend more time together,
maybe do some traveling
and see the world.
Well, just look
at us now.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Yeah. Life sure is
full of surprises.
[SCREAMS]
Stop him!
Kill him!
[GRUNTS]
MINISTER: For better or worse,
for richer or poorer,
in sickness and in health,
till death do you part.
[GASPING]
Congratulations.
You may now kiss the bride.
Huh?
A true classic
never goes out of style.
That was good.
WOMAN ON TV: ls it true that Jesse and
Jade may in fact be the serial killers
that you've been tracking
for the past few days?
MAN: We have some...
We can't confirm
that at this time.
The previous murders appear to
be the work of just one killer.
It's possible, actually, it's possible
that one of them is a hostage
or simply unaware of
what the other is up to.
WOMAN: Detective?
For the time being, in the absence
of any other information,
these kids have to be considered
armed and extremely dangerous.
[INAUDIBLE]
First thing tomorrow morning,
we deliver the dolls.
We collect our money.
We're gonna need it.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh!
Excuse me.
The, uh, door was open.
I didn't realize
there was anybody in here.
Russ! I thought
we were getting a suite.
[ROARING]
Whoa!
Who's this?
I thought we were
getting a suite.
No. This is our room.
Oh. [LAUGHING]
Oh!
Russ!
Look. Have you ever seen anything
so cute in your whole life?
What a great idea for a wedding gift.
She's beautiful.
Oh.
Well, this little guy has a
face only a mother could love.
Hi. I'm Chucky, and I
wouldn't talk if I were you.
Hi-de-ho.
Chucky! Of course. I remember.
He was a Good Guy doll.
They were programmed
to say all kinds of shit.
Ooh.
Well, I don't
like him at all.
You know, you two really make
a delicious-looking couple.
Hey, Diane,
don't you think?
Oh, absolutely.
I mean, imagine what their
children are gonna look like, huh?
Listen,
it's getting late, and. . .
So, what are you guys
up to tonight? Hmm?
JADE: It's our wedding night.
Well, so what are
you watching TV for?
Well, you see, it's our
wedding night as well,
which is what makes
this just so perfect.
You know what they say?
"The more, the merrier."
Okay, yeah. No.
You know what? We're really tired.
Gotta get to bed early.
Okay, well,
we'll be right next door.
Okay.
That thieving slut.
She doesn't deserve
to wear that ring.
To us.
Oh, Russ, give me a break.
We are, technically,
on our honeymoon, remember?
Yeah, well, it was your idea
to come here, not mine.
I told you we'd have seen more
action at Club Med. [GASPS]
Come on, we're here.
Let's make the best of it.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[MOANING]
Ohh! [LAUGHS]
Yeah, baby, come on.
Yeah. Come on.
[WHIMPERING]
Huh?
[BOTH SCREAM]
I love you.
I should have asked you
this a long time ago.
Tiffany, will you
be my bride?
Oh, Chucky.
Yes. Yes.
[GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLES]
[CONTINUES GRUNTING]
Ah !
[LAUGHS]
[GASPS] Oh!
Chucky.
[WEEPING]
Why are you crying?
I always cry at weddings.
Oh, my God.
I'm crying.
I wonder if all
the plumbing works.
Well, I don't know about you, but I'm
starting to feel like Pinocchio here.
Ohh!
I am anatomically correct,
you know.
Ohh!
[MOANING]
[BOTH MOANING]
Wait. Wait.
What? What? What?
Have you got a rubber?
Have I got a rubber?
Yeah.
Tiff!
What?
Look at me.
I'm all rubber.
Oh, that's right. Wait.
I thought you were plastic.
Tiff.
What?
Kiss me.
Okay.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
David, it's me.
Jade!
Where are you?
Niagara.
The Honeymoon Sweets motel,
which, believe me, is even
worse than it sounds.
Are you okay?
No. I'm married.
ls that bad?
I'm really scared.
I think, maybe
he did it, David.
I think Jesse has
totally lost it.
Jesus.
What should I do?
Are you sure?
Pretty sure.
Then you've got to
go to the police.
I don't think I can.
I still love him.
ls that wrong?
[BEEPS]
Hold on a second.
Hello?
David, it's me.
Hey, Jesse.
I'm sorry to
call you so late.
I got a problem.
It's Jade.
Listen to me.
Go to the police.
Now, before
somebody else gets hurt.
Yoo-hoo!
Anybody here?
Housekeeping!
[SIGHS] Hello?
Housekeeping.
Joy to be here.
Okay. Oh, my. . .
Newlyweds.
[CHUCKLES]
What the heck went on here?
[HUMMING]
[SCREAMING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
I can't do this.
What?
I can't go
with you, Jesse.
Not anymore.
[SIGHS]
Oh, man, I'm glad
you said that first.
Why?
Jade, this is
too much for me.
I love you.
I will always love you.
But there is a limit
to how much I can take.
Would you please stop talking to
me like I'm the one who's crazy?
You're the crazy one!
You're the mass murderer!
You mean multiple murderer.
So you admit it?
No, I don't!
I can't take
this shit anymore.
[SCREAMS]
Anyway, the thing that struck me
was how sure you both sounded.
And to me, that meant
one of three things.
One of you is lying,
both of you are whacko,
or both of you are wrong.
Add to that the fact that I know
you both better than anybody else,
and I've never seen either of
you so much as hurt a fly,
and I've concluded
that what we have here
is a terrible
misunderstanding.
Do you guys smell something in here?
[SNIFFING]
JESSE: Okay,
for the sake of argument,
if it wasn't you,
and it wasn't me,
then who else would want to
kill Warren and Needlenose?
And those people
from last night.
You're assuming Warren's dead.
He's only missing.
You're suggesting
that Warren. . .
Yes! Why not?
I'd buy him as a psychopath
before either of you two.
Pooh ! Something
really stinks in here.
I told you not to leave
your dirty socks back there.
Honey, this ain't no dirty socks.
[SNIFFING]
[GASPS]
I feel like such an idiot.
Me, too.
JESSE: I mean, I can't believe I
thought that you could kill someone.
I know. I'm so sorry.
David, what would
we do without you?
What do you mean,
"Without me?"
I mean you set us straight.
We owe you one.
You're a good friend.
The best.
[COCKS GUN]
Pull over!
Pull over now!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
David, come on, buddy, it's me.
Come on, let's talk this over.
I'm not your buddy.
Fuck, David!
Please put the gun down.
Why? So you can
kill me too?
We didn't kill anybody.
Oh, you're good. You're good!
You even had me fooled.
What are you
talking about?
This!
[BOTH GASP]
You son of a bitch!
David, I didn't do it.
She did it!
I would never. . .
Shut up!
Hey, help! Over here!
[SIREN BLARES]
Nobody move!
[GASPS] Oh, my God!
[HORN BLARES]
No!
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
That works too.
Get this heap of shit moving !
Now! Now! Now!
[SIREN WAILING]
[CACKLING]
I imagine at this point you two
must have a lot of questions.
You do know who I am?
Chucky.
And this is Tiffany.
I believe we've already met,
haven't we, sweetface?
So, how did you
end up like this?
Well, it's a long story.
lt sure is.
ln fact,
if it was a movie,
it would take three or four
sequels just to do it justice.
What are you
gonna do with us?
Funny you should ask.
These bodies are okay.
But they're like apartments
that we're just renting.
But now
we're movin' on up.
Like George and Weezie.
And we're looking to buy.
And you know what they
say about real estate.
Location, location, location.
Well, you guys are definitely in
the right place at the wrong time.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
MAN ON RADIO: This is a
WEBH special report.
The Jesse and Jade case keeps
getting weirder and weirder.
Fingerprints discovered
at two separate crime scenes
have been identified as
belonging to Charles Lee Ray,
the notorious serial killer
gunned down in 1988.
Now police confirm that Ray's
corpse will be exhumed
from a Hackensack, New Jersey
cemetery sometime today.
What? Chucky, the Heart of Damballa!
I know! What'll we do?
What'll we do?
Shut up!
Just let me think, okay?
First we gotta
get some new wheels.
Every cop within 500 miles
is looking for this van.
We need something inconspicuous,
but with a little style.
Hold still, honey, or I'm gonna
poke you in the eye again.
[TIFFANY HUMMING]
Yes. I believe I'm going to
look absolutely ravishing.
[BELL DINGS]
[CONTINUES HUMMING]
[GASPS] Excuse me.
Nobody makes Swedish
meatballs like you, babe.
Peachy!
Thanks, honey pot.
I hope you left
room for dessert.
You know it, pooky.
[KISSES]
[TIFFANY HUMMING]
You know, if I had known that
marriage was such a great gig,
I would never have waited
this long to tie the knot.
On the other hand, she's not
much of a housekeeper, is she?
CHUCKY: Tiff?
Huh?
Those dishes aren't gonna
wash themselves, you know.
You were nice enough
to cook for him.
The least he could do
is wash the dish.
Oh!
What are you doing?
[YELLS]
What would
Martha Stewart say?
Fuck Martha Stewart.
Martha Stewart can kiss
my shiny plastic butt.
Here I am slaving away
over a hot stove,
making cookies, making Swedish
meatballs, and for what?
For a man who
doesn't appreciate me.
For a man who can't even
wash one fucking dish.
For a man who isn't even
a man at all where it counts,
if you get my drift.
Take it from me, honey.
Plastic is no substitute
for a nice hunk of wood.
I didn't hear her
complaining last night.
Any guy would need a hunk of
plastic, probably battery-operated,
to get a reaction
out of you in bed.
And by the way,
where the hell did you
learn to bake?
How dare you
speak to me that way!
You started it!
I did not!
No!
[SCREAMS]
Whoa!
Jesse? Jesse, please.
Please. Oh, God.
Jesse?
[METAL SCREECHING]
[WHIMPERING]
[SCREAMING]
Get me out of here!
[SCREAMING STOPS]
TIFFANY: [SCREAMING]
You bitch !
[SCREAMS]
[GROWLING]
Jade!
Hurry!
Go, go, go!
Not without you !
I'll be right behind you !
CHUCKY: Hey, beautiful.
[SCREAMS]
[TIFFANY MOANING]
Aah!
Jade!
Move it!
[YELLS] Ow!
[TIFFANY GROANING IN PAIN]
[DIRT SHOVELING]
[GUNSHOT]
[SCREAMING]
Get down there. Move!
Open the coffin, Jade.
Hurry up. I'm trying,
you fucking midget!
[GUNSHOT]
[SCREAMS]
[SQUEAKING]
Ugh!
Ugh! You really
didn't need to see that.
Give me the amulet.
Oh!
Bitch! You broke my neck.
[SCREAMS]
[THUNDERCLAP]
Let her go.
Let Jade go first.
Get moving.
And Jade?
See you real soon.
Get out of here.
Why can't I ever get it on
with the real good guys?
You're a lucky girl.
[SOBBING]
Catch me, Chucky.
[MOANS]
[COUGHING]
Ugh !
Aah! [GROANS]
JADE: Oh, God, no!
God, no!
Pull it out.
[WHIMPERING]
[GROANING]
I'll take that.
It's show time.
[CHUCKY CHANTING]
Give me the power,
I beg of you !
[CHANTING]
This is it.
I love you, Chucky.
I know.
We belong together,
forever.
Kiss me.
Hah!
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
Why?
Oh, Chucky, look at us.
Don't you see?
We belong dead.
Goodbye, darling.
I'll see you in hell.
[SIGHS]
[GROWLING]
[YELLS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[MOANING]
[SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
My mother always told me
love would set me free.
Get off my knife.
[SCREAMING]
[RATS SQUEAKING]
Let me see your hands!
Drop the gun! Drop it!
[CHUCKY SCREAMING]
Let me out! Let me out!
[YELLING]
Whoa.
Don't move!
[THUNDERCLAP]
Go ahead and shoot.
I'll be back.
I always come back.
[GROANS] But dying
is such a bitch.
[GROANING]
No one's ever gonna believe this.
You know that?
What's gonna
happen to us?
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Preston. Yeah,
I'm here now.
I'm afraid we've got another
corpse to add to the list.
Jesse and Jade?
Hell, they didn't do it.
Just get forensics
down here.
You're never gonna
fucking believe this.
Right.
You two go on home.
And stay put.
Let's go home.
Ooh.
Jesus.
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Goddamn! Son of a bitch!
Holy. . .
[WAILING]
Bitch! Jesus!
[SCREAMING]
[BAWLING]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[Man]
♪ Here's to my mother ♪
♪ From her tribe
I have crawled ♪
♪ Get on my feet I walk
three steps then I fall ♪
♪ Don't try to save me, mama
Don't kiss my wounded knees ♪
♪ I won't go home now, mama
Don't make a fool of me ♪
♪ You see I am
the boogie-woogie king ♪
♪ Yes, yes ♪
♪ Take my hand
Take my other hand ♪
♪ Take my hand ♪
♪ Boogie-woogie king
from the mountaintop ♪
♪ Is what I am ♪
♪ The boogie-woogie king
from the mountaintop ♪
♪ Is what I am ♪
♪ The people watch me
ride this wicked mule ♪
♪ From its stall ♪
♪ Into the streets where
a thousand eyes stare at all ♪
♪ What do you see now, mama ♪
♪ This wicked mule and me ♪
♪ Or do you see a child
try to get a gal to leave ♪
♪ See, I am
the boogie-woogie king ♪
♪ Yes, yes ♪
♪ Take my hand
Take my other hand ♪
♪ Take my hand ♪
♪ Boogie-woogie king
from the mountaintop ♪
♪ Is what I am ♪
♪ Yes, the boogie-woogie king
from the mountaintop ♪
♪ Boogie-woogie king
from the mountaintop ♪♪
from the mountaintop ♪
♪ Is what I am ♪♪
TIFFANY: We belong dead.
[HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Obsessive acts of hate ♪
♪ Abductions
and mass torture ♪
♪ Create emotions
of vengeance ♪
♪ When the living
become the dead ♪
♪ Home invasion ♪
♪ Private party
of thieves ♪
♪ Blood spilled
material thrill ♪
♪ A sign of the times ♪
♪ Self-destruction ♪
♪ A human disease ♪
♪ Jealousy killed the queen
Sliced her neck from ear to ear ♪
♪ Money and power
set the king free ♪
♪ A jury of his peers
let him be ♪
♪ Jealousy killed the queen
Sliced her neck from ear to ear ♪
♪ Money and power
set the king free ♪
♪ A jury of his peers
let him be ♪
♪ Jealousy killed the queen
Sliced her neck from ear to ear ♪
♪ Money and power
set the king free ♪
CHUCKY: That's more like it.
[LAUGHING]